ICICI credential Life Insurance Company
Limited is a joint venture between ICI
Bank limited and credential Corporation
Holdings the company offers a range of
products and services such as life
insurance or wealth management and
retirement planning
Solutions ICI credential Pension funds
Management Company Limited and ICI
credential trust limited are other
subsidiaries ICI credential
International life insurance offers Life
Insurance Solutions in the United
Kingdom Dubai and Singapore for Su of
ICI credential life insurance plans term
insurance ICICI prei protect smart and
return of Premium saving plans ICI pre
gift Pro and ICI pre guaranteed Pension
Plan flexi unit link insurance plans 's
ICI PR signature online and ICI PR smart
life retirement plans ICICI preal
pension plan and ICICI preg guaranteed
Pension Plan Flexi child plan ICI smart
kid with ICI Smart Life others money
back plans health insurance and credit
life or Group
Insurance have complaints ICI credential
life insurance has a three- tier
grievance redressal mechanism to address
the policy holders concerns policy
holders can initiate the resolution of
the insurance issues by filing
complaints with the customer support
team if necessary concerns can be
escalated to the grievance redressal
officer grro and corporate office of
ICICI prudent as a last resort policy
holders can approach the insurance
Ombudsman of the insurance Regulatory
and Development Authority of India there
for resolution common issues are delayed
settlement of insurance policies Emi
claims and ICI credential life insurance
payments Level One customer care ICICI
credential life insurance ICICI
credential life insurance has a multitud
approach approach for policy holders to
address concerns in level one they can
contact the toll-free customer care
submit online complaints through the
portal or mobile app or send a complaint
letter to the local grievance redressal
officer complaints can also be initiated
through the integrated grievance
management system MMS of a or the
National Consumer helpline required
details for filing a complaint include
ICI credential life insurance policy
number communication details such such
as phone number and name avoid sharing
personal or sensitive information a
concise description of the issue about
the insurance policy or any other
concerns ICICI credential customer care
number to register a complaint with
ICICI credential life insurance please
use the toll-free customer care numbers
provided below Additionally you can
click on the numbers and email addresses
to connect with customer support ICC
credential life insurance complaint
number 1 8626
67766 email Lifeline at iff.com
customer care number NRI + 9180 6938
5555 WhatsApp number + 919 92066
7766 email claim support claim support
at ICI pr.com
policy helpline number by
80-67
9777 1860 to 67
9997 email by online at iff.com file an
online complaint the most direct method
to register a grievance with ICICI
credential life insurance is via the
online portal accessing the portal or
using the ICI credential life mobile app
allows for easy filing of an online
complaint note for for concerns about
insurance policies approach the National
Consumer helpline NCH and the integrated
grievance management system IGS provided
by the insurance Regulatory and
Development Authority there file an
online complaint to ICI Prudential Life
regarding Insurance products and
services complain online to ICICI
credential life
insurance final complaint make an
insurance claim click here track policy
claim status click here email Lifeline
at iff.com group and annuity customer
support register a complaint about group
or annuity corporate insurance plans to
ICICI credential customer care
number 1860 2661
999 email my at ICI pri.com
complain online to
ICICI make a complaint level two
grievance redressal officer ICI
credential life insurance in the case of
unsatisfactory or unresolved complaints
with ICICI credential life insurance
policy holders have the option to
escalate the matter to the grievance
redressal officer at Regional branches
and corporate offices if dissatisfied
even after the final order or if the
complaint remains unresolved for over 2
weeks further escalate the matter to the
grievance redressing committee GRC at
the head office of the ICI credential
life note escalation should be initiated
within 60 days of receiving a response
Bea Bosa an integrated grievance
management system igms of is also
available for escalation purposes when
submitting a grievance form include the
following required information unique
service request Sr number policy number
the subject of unsatisfactory redressal
of the complaint descript ion of the
grievance reason for
dissatisfaction attach copies of
relevant documents if required to
escalate the matter send an email or
write to the grievance redressal officer
at the head office of ICI credential
life insurance using the provided
contact information designation
grievance redressal officer ICICI
credential life email grow at ICICI
pr.com
online form click to complaint
address ICICI credential life insurance
SC limited unit number 1 a and twoa
tipco Plaza Rani Sati Mar Malad East
Mumbai
497 level three grievance redressal
committee GC if your lodged complaint is
not resolved to your expectation by the
grievance redressal officer then
escalate the disputed matter to the
grievance redressal committee GC at the
head office of ICI credential Life
Insurance Company Company Limited with a
reference ticket number of the previous
complaint submit a complaint online or
send a written grievance letter to GSI
at the postal address below designation
grievance redressive committee ICI
credential life online form make a
complaint post an address grievance
redressing committee head office ICICI
credential life insurance go limited
unit number 1 a and TOA tipco Plaza Rani
s Mar Malad East Mumbai
497 note if registered complaints with
ICICI credential life insurance remain
unresolved for more than 30 days policy
holders can file a complaint with the
insurance Ombudsman or in Insurance
Regulatory and Development Authority of
India insurance
utsman as for the IR regulations
insurance companies including ICI
credential life insurance are obligated
to resolve complaints related to
insurance policies within 30 days if
policy holders are dissatisfied with
ICICI credential life's resolution they
have the right to petition the insurance
Ombudsman under the 2023 Insurance
Ombudsman rules click file an online
grievance to the insurance
onsman alternatively for assistance if
the dispute is not resolved within 30
days or if policyholders are not
satisfied with a grievance redressal
committee's final decision they can
email in scount at s.
cod.in regulatory
Authority if ICI credential life
insurance ctd has violated your consumer
rights or if there are disputes related
to insurance claims or payments you can
seek compensation by approaching the
following
authorities internal arbitration op for
internal arbitration with ICICI
credential life insurance Co LTD to
resolve Insurance disputes within the
company you may use the online smart odr
platform for insurance standards
register complaints online regarding
Insurance standards with the insurance
Regulatory and Development Authority of
India there for financial matters large
Financial complaints against the
insurance company with the banking
utsman
RBI consumer commission depending on the
compensation amount you can submit your
complaint to the appropriate consumer
commission such as the National Consumer
disputes redressal commission ncdrc
through the designated online platform
legal action if you are dissatisfied
with the final decisions or orders from
ICI credential life insurance and
Regulatory bodies and want to take legal
action you can file a case online using
the link below click file a case online
by a filing to District High courts
important note before taking legal
action it is advisable to seek advice
from legal professionals to understand
applicable laws your legal rights the
legal process and alternative options
such as arbitration with the insurance
company